<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<ModMetaData>
    <packageId>wishRobber.theantagonist</packageId>
    <name>The Antagonist</name>
    <author>wishRobber</author>
    <description>The Antagonist is a custom AI storyteller for RimWorld that knows how strong you really are.

Most storytellers size their threats from colony wealth and head-count, which badly under-reads a levelled party - a level 300 hero in plain gear looks "cheap", so late-game raids turn into a formality. The Antagonist reads your ISEKAI RPG Leveling levels and grows with your heroes: as they climb the ranks, it hits back harder, up to roughly 4.5x the normal threat budget at max level.

Its threat scaling is power-weighted, so one strong hero raises the danger for the whole party - you cannot hide a max-level carry behind nine rookies. It never makes the game easier than normal; it only ever escalates.

Event pacing follows a rising curve of challenge and tension: it pushes you with dangerous events, gives you breathing room, then comes back to push once more.

Requires ISEKAI RPG Leveling. Ships with a placeholder portrait. Safe to add to or remove from any save at any time, and pairs perfectly with the Improved Defaults mod, which can pre-select The Antagonist automatically for every new game.</description>
    <supportedVersions>
        <li>1.6</li>
    </supportedVersions>
    <modDependencies>
        <li>
            <packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
            <displayName>Harmony</displayName>
            <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
        </li>
        <li>
            <packageId>JellyCreative.IsekaiLeveling</packageId>
            <displayName>ISEKAI RPG LEVELING</displayName>
            <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/3657580708</steamWorkshopUrl>
        </li>
    </modDependencies>
    <loadAfter>
        <li>brrainz.harmony</li>
        <li>JellyCreative.IsekaiLeveling</li>
    </loadAfter>
</ModMetaData>
