<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<ModMetaData>
    <packageId>wishRobber.theantagonist</packageId>
    <name>The Antagonist</name>
    <author>wishRobber</author>
    <description>The Antagonist is a custom AI storyteller for RimWorld - a new face on the Choose AI Storyteller screen alongside Cassandra Classic, Phoebe Chillax and Randy Random. It knows how strong you really are.

The Antagonist scales its threats to your party's actual power, not just your stuff. Vanilla storytellers size raids from colony wealth and head-count, which badly under-reads a levelled party - a level 300 hero in plain gear looks "cheap", so late-game raids turn into a formality. The Antagonist reads your ISEKAI RPG Leveling levels and grows with your heroes: as they climb the ranks, it hits back harder (up to roughly 4.5x the normal threat budget at max level).

Its threat scaling is power-weighted, so one strong hero raises the danger for the whole party - you cannot hide a max-level carry behind nine rookies. It never makes the game easier than normal; it only ever escalates.

Event pacing currently follows Cassandra's classic rising curve of challenge and tension. It ships with a placeholder portrait.

ISEKAI RPG Leveling is optional - without it, The Antagonist simply plays as a standard Cassandra-style storyteller. Safe to add to or remove from any save at any time. Pairs perfectly with the Improved Defaults mod, which can pre-select The Antagonist automatically for every new game.

Keywords: custom storyteller, AI storyteller mod, new storyteller, scaling difficulty, Isekai, RPG leveling, difficulty, events, raids.</description>
    <supportedVersions>
        <li>1.6</li>
    </supportedVersions>
    <modDependencies>
        <li>
            <packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
            <displayName>Harmony</displayName>
            <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
        </li>
    </modDependencies>
    <loadAfter>
        <li>brrainz.harmony</li>
        <li>JellyCreative.IsekaiLeveling</li>
    </loadAfter>
</ModMetaData>
